Guide to the Anson Phelps Stokes Family Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
In addition, the organization or institution which a given individual represents is indicated alongside the name. This can be of assistance in two ways. First, an individual name which does happen to appear in the folder listings, such as Thomas Jesse Jones, may be identified by means of the list as the director of the Phelps-Stokes Fund. Second, a researcher looking for the correspondence of a given organization or project can use this information in Appendix I to discover which correspondents are of interest.
A note of caution should be added here on the limitations of the list. No attempt was made to indicate every person who corresponded with Anson Phelps Stokes. Some individuals who do appear on the list have not been identified as to organization, institution, or position, for a variety of reasons: they did not represent an institution, they had retired, the name of their employer was not deemed significant, their name needed no identification to the general public, and so forth. Individuals on the list are identified according to the capacity in which they corresponded with Anson Phelps Stokes. George Wharton Pepper, for a time U.S. Senator from Pennsylvania, is identified with Washington Cathedral, since his correspondence with Anson Phelps Stokes is oriented towards his role as Chairman of the Executive Committee of the Cathedral rather than towards his political activities.
In general, Stokes's basic filing system was maintained. In some cases, correspondence was filed under the name of the organization or institution as well as under the names of individuals. This was usually material of a general nature newsletters, bulletins, etc. which did not emanate from major officials or their offices. For this reason, the names of organizations occasionally appear on the list in addition to the names of officials within the organizations.
SELECT LIST OF CORRESPONDENTS, 1892 - 1921
Angell, James Rowland --- President of Yale University
American University Union
Beers, Clifford --- National Committee for Mental Hygiene
Bingham, Hiram
Bliss, Frederick Jones
Brent, The Rt. Rev. Charles H. --- Bishop of Western New York
Buttrick, Wallace --- General Education Board
Capen, Samuel P. --- American Council on Education
Cavert, Samuel McCrea --- Committee on the War and the Religious Outlook, Federal Council of Churches
Coffin, Henry Sloane
Coit, J.H. --- Alumni Association of St. Paul's School, Concord, N.H.
Cunliffe, J.W. --- American University Union
Day, George Parmly
Dodge, Cleveland H. --- Robert College at Constantinople
Drury, Dr. Samuel --- St. Paul's School, Concord, N.H.
Duggan, Stephen P. --- Institute of International Education
Farnam, Henry W. --- China Famine Fund
Farrand, Max --- The Commonwealth Fund
Flexner, Dr. Abraham --- General Education Board
Grenfell, Dr. Wilfred T. --- Labrador
Hadley, Arthur Twining --- President of Yale University
Howland, Charles P.
James, Dr. Walter B. --- Trudeau Sanatorium
Keogh, Andrew --- Librarian of Yale University
Krans, Horatio S. --- American University Union
Lobenstine, Ed --- China Continuation Committee of the National Missionary Conference
Macfarland, Charles S. --- General Secretary of the Federal Council of Churches
McCulloch, James W. --- Phelps-Stokes Estates
Mitchell, Clarence Blair
Moton, Robert R. --- Tuskegee Institute
Nettleton, George H. --- American University Union
Oldham, J.H. --- Emergency Committee of Co-Operating Missions
Parsons, The Rt. Rev. Edward L. --- Bishop Coadjutor of California
Peabody, George Foster --- re: study of African music
Reid, Gilbert --- International Institute of China
Rockefeller, John D. Jr.
Roosevelt, Theodore
St. Paul's School
Sakai, Barnabas T.
Seymour, George Dudley
Sloane, John --- Y.M.C.A.
Staub, Albert W. --- American University of Beirut
Taft, William Howard
Thorne, Samuel
Thurston, Matilda C. --- President of Ginling College, Nanking, China
Vickrey, Charles V. --- Near East Relief
Welsh, Lewis S.
Whittemore, Oscar M.
Woofter, T.J. Jr. --- Phelps-Stokes Fund
SELECT LIST OF CORRESPONDENTS, 1922-1930 May 31
Acheson, Barclay --- Near East Relief
Ackerman, Carl W.
Adee, George T.
Adler, Cyrus --- American Jewish Committee
Aery, William Anthony --- Hampton Institute
Aggrey, J.E.K.
Aggrey, Mrs. Rose D.
Alderman, Edwin A. --- President of the University of Virginia
Alexander, Eugene D. --- Alumni Association of St. Paul's School
Alexander, Will W. --- Director of the Commission on Inter-Racial Co-Operation
American Red Cross
American Relief Administration
American University at Cairo
Ames, J.S. --- President of Johns Hopkins University
Andrews, C.F. --- Phelps-Stokes Fund (India)
Anet, Henri --- Bureau des Missions Protestantes du Congo Belge
Angell, James Rowland --- President of Yale University
Angier, Roswell P. --- Dean of Freshmen, Yale University
Anthony, B.K. --- Yale-in-China
Appleget, Thomas B. --- Laura-Spelman Rockefeller Fund
Archer, Laird W. --- Near East Relief
Armitage, Clyde F. --- Near East Relief
Arnett, Trevor --- General Education Board
Arnold, Lauren --- Yale-in-China
Arthur, George R. --- Julius Rosenwald Fund
Ascension Farm School
Associated Charities of Washington, D.C.
Atkins, S.G. --- Winston-Salem Teachers' College
Austin, Chellis A. --- President of the Seaboard National Bank
Bachman, Frank P. --- General Education Board
Baker, George Barr --- American Relief Administration
Bakewell, Charles M. --- Yale University; Chairman of the Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
Baldwin, William H. --- National Cathedral Foundation
Barton, James L. --- American Board of Commissioners for Foreign Missions
Baskervill, The Rev. E.L. --- Archdeacon for Work among the Negroes, Diocese of North Carolina
Battey, Cornelius M. --- Tuskegee Institute (photography)
Beers, Clifford W. --- National Committee for Mental Hygiene
Behringer, Emma P. --- Personal Accounts, Phelps-Stokes Estates
Belknap, Chauncey --- China Medical Board
Berry, Gordon L. --- Institute of International Education
Bethune, Mary McLeod --- President of Bethune-Cookman College
Bevis, Palmer --- Yale-in-China
Bicknell, Col. Ernest P. --- Vice-Chairman, American National Red Cross re: Russian refugee relief
Bingham, Dr. Arthur W. --- Williard Parker Hospital, N.Y.C.
Bingham, Hiram --- Lt. Governor of Connecticut; U.S. Senate
Bird, Charles S. Jr. --- Russian Refugee Relief Society
Boardman, Mabel T. --- Secretary of the American Red Cross
Bohanon, The Very Rev. Franklin J. --- Washington Cathedral
Bouimistrow, Wladimir W. --- Russian Refugee Relief Society
Branch, Dr. J.B. --- Peking Union Medical College
Brawley, Benjamin --- The Home Mission College Review
Bratenahl, The Very Rev. G.C.F. --- Washington Cathedral
Brent, The Rt. Rev. Charles H. --- Bishop of Western New York; American Church Institute for Negroes
Brierley, W.W. --- International Education Board; General Education Board
Bristol, Rear Admiral Mark L. --- American Hospital of Constantinople
Brookings, Robert S. --- Institute of Economics, Washington, D.C.
Brown, Charles R. --- Dean of Yale Divinity School
Brown, Elmer E. --- Chancellor of New York University
Brown, Harry W. Jr. --- National Cathedral Association
Brown, John Crosby --- Yale-in-China Campaign
Brown, William Adams --- Union Theological Seminary
Burroughs, Nannie H. --- National Training School for Women and Girls
Butler, Nicholas Murray --- President of Columbia University; President of Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
Buttrick, Wallace --- General Education Board
Caldwell, R.J. --- Russian refugee relief
Campbell, E. Fay --- Yale University Christian Association
Campbell, T.M. --- U.S. Department of Agriculture, Tuskegee, Alabama
Carter, Edward C. --- American Council Institute of Pacific Relations
Carter, William H. --- Tuskegee Institute
Carter, William S. --- The Rockefeller Foundation
Capen, Samuel P. --- American Council on Education
Castle, William R. --- Assistant Secretary of State
The Century Club
Cholerton, F.E. --- Advisory Committee on Education, Phelps-Stokes Fund in Liberia
Chorley, Kenneth --- re: Russian refugee relief
Coffin, Henry Sloane --- President of Union Theological Seminary
Colgate, Russell
Colladay, The Very Rev. Samuel R. --- Christ Church Cathedral, Hartford, Ct.
Colton, E.T. --- International Committee of the Y.M.C.A.
The Community Chest of Washington, D.C.
Cooper, William Knowles
Cromwell, Mary E. --- St. Anna's Home
Cross, Wilbur --- Dean of Yale University Graduate School
Cunliffe, J.W. --- American University Union
Darby, William L. --- Washington Federation of Churches
Darst, The Rt. Rev. Thomas C. --- National Commission on Evangelism, The Bishops' Crusade
Davies, The Rt. Rev. Thomas F. --- Bishop of Western Massachusetts
Davis, Arthur V. --- Yale-in-China
Davis, Major Claflin --- Russian refugee relief
Davis, Jackson --- General Education Board
Day, Clive --- Yale Professor of Economic History
Day, George Parmly --- Yale University Press; Treasurer of Yale University
Dayton, Arthur Bliss --- Dean of Yale Medical School, Yale-in-China
Delafield, Frederick S.
Delano, Frederic A. --- Chairman, Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund; Community Chest of Washington, D.C.
Denison, Robert C. --- Pomona College
DeSilver, Albert --- American Civil Liberties Union
Devine, Edward T. --- Dean of the Graduate School, American University
Dillard, James H. --- General Education Board; Slater Fund; Phelps-Stokes Fund Board
Dodge, Cleveland E. --- Laura-Spelman Rockefeller Fund Board
Donohugh, Thomas S. --- Board of Foreign Missions of the Methodist Episcopal Church
Dowd, Rachel A. --- Yale-in-China
Drury, Dr. Samuel --- St. Paul's School, Concord, N.H.
DuBois, W.E.B. --- re: Thomas Jesse Jones and the Phelps-Stokes Fund
Duggan, Stephen P. --- Institute of International Education
Dulles, Allen W. --- Chief of the Division of Near Eastern Affairs, U.S. State Department
Durkee, J. Stanley --- President of Howard University
Eastman, George --- Eastman Kodak Company
Edwards, R.H. --- The National Council on Religion in Higher Education
Eggleston, Margery F. --- China Medical Board of the Rockefeller Foundation
Eliot, Charles William --- President of Harvard University
Embree, Edwin R. --- The Julius Rosenwald Fund; The Rockefeller Foundation
Emhardt, The Rev. William Chauncey --- National Council of the Protestant Episcopal Church
Evans, Henry R. --- Bureau of Education, Department of the Interior
Farnam, Henry W.
Farnam, Thomas W. --- Associate Treasurer and Comptroller, Yale University
Farrand, Max --- Yale University
Federal Council of Churches
Fisher, Samuel H. --- Yale-in-China
Flexner, Dr. Abraham --- General Education Board
Flint, Joseph M.
Foote, Arthur E. --- U.S. Secretary of Commerce
Ford, Henry
Foreman, Clark --- Phelps-Stokes Fund
Fosdick, Raymond B. --- General Education Board; Rockefeller Foundation
Fraser, A.C. --- Achimota College, Gold Coast
Furst, Clyde --- The Carnegie Foundation
Gammack, The Rev. Arthur
Gibson, B.D. --- International Missionary Council
Gildersleeve, Virginia C. --- President of Barnard College
Goetchius, John M. --- St. Paul's School, Concord, N.H.
Gollock, G.A. --- International Review of Missions; Educational Commission to E. Africa of the Phelps-Stokes Fund
Goodrich, Chauncey W. --- Federal Council of Churches
Grant, U.S. III --- National Capital Park and Planning Commission
Greene, Roger S. --- China Medical Board of the Rockefeller Foundation
Gregg, James E. --- Principal of Hampton Institute
Griggs, Maitland F.
Griswold, The Rev. Latta --- Trinity Church, Lenox, Mass.
Grosvenor, Gilbert --- National Geographic Society
Guggisberg, Sir Gordon --- Governor of the Gold Coast
Gulick, Sidney L. --- Federal Council of Churches
Hadley, Arthur T. --- Former President of Yale University
Hail, William J. --- Yale-in-China
Hammond, D.Q. --- John Price Jones Corporation; Hampton Institute; Tuskegee Institute
Hare, Charles W. --- Tuskegee Institute
Hart, Charles D. --- St. Paul's School
Harvey, Edwin D. --- Yale-in-China
Haskell, Henry S. --- Carnegie Endowment for International Peace
Haynes, George E. --- Federal Council of Churches
Holsey, Albon L. --- National Negro Business League
Holt, Hamilton --- President of Rollins College, Fla.
Hoover, Herbert --- U.S. Secretary of Commerce
Howard, Sir Esme --- British Ambassador to the U.S.
Howe, Walter B. --- Yale Endowment Fund
Howland, Charles P. --- General Education Board; Rockefeller Foundation; Council on Foreign Relations
Hume, Dr. Edward H. --- President of Yale-in-China
Husband, W.W. --- Second Assistant Secretary, U.S. Department of Labor
Hutcheson, Major General Grote --- National Cathedral Foundation
Hutchins, Francis S. --- Treasurer of Yale-in-China
Hutchinson, C.A. --- Tuskegee Institute
Hyman, Joseph C. --- American Jewish Joint Distribution Committee re: Russian refugee relief
Ignatieff, Count Paul N. --- Russian Red Cross
Ihlder, John --- Pittsburgh Housing Association
Ingersoll, Charles E. --- St. Paul's School
Jackson, W.M. --- Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
James, Arthur Curtiss
Jameson, J. Franklin --- The American Historical Review
Jennings, Coleman
John Price Jones Corporation
Johnson, Allen --- Dictionary of American Biography
Johnson, Homer H. --- Yale-in-China
Johnson, James Weldon --- N.A.A.C.P.
Johnson, Mordecai W. --- President of Howard University
Johnson, Major T.F. --- Assistant High Commissioner for Refugees, League of Nations
Jones, Frederick S. --- Dean of Yale College
Jones, Dr. Thomas E. --- President of Fisk University
Jones, Dr. Thomas Jesse --- Phelps-Stokes Fund
Jones, William H. --- Howard University
Keigwin, H.S. --- Director of Native Development, Salisbury, Southern Rhodesia
Kelsey, Clarence H. --- Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
Kent, Charles F. --- National Council on Religion in Higher Education
Keogh, Andrew --- Librarian, Yale University
Keppel, Frederick P. --- President of the Carnegie Corporation
Ketcham, George F. --- Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
Klots, Allen T.
Konovaloff, Alexandre --- Russian Zemstvos and Towns Relief Committee
Krans, Horatio S. --- American University Union
Kreuger, J.W. --- American Relief Administration re: Russian refugee relief
Lansill, John --- John Price Jones Corporation; Peabody Education Program; Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
Laura Spelman Rockefeller Foundation
Leavens, Dickson H. --- Yale-in-China, Treasurer
Leigh, Robert D. --- President of Bennington College
Lewis, Edwin N. --- National Cathedral Foundation
Lewis, William Mather --- President of George Washington University
Lindley, Grace --- Woman's Auxiliary of the National Council of the Protestant Episcopal Church
Lines, The Rt. Rev. Edwin S. --- Bishop of Newark, N.J.
Lloyd, Elizabeth --- Phelps-Stokes Fund
Lobenstine, The Rev. E.C. --- National Christian Council of China
Loram, Dr. C.T. --- Education Commission to East Africa, Phelps-Stokes Fund
MacGrath, R. --- Russian Refugee Relief Society
MacKenzie, W. Douglas --- President of the Hartford Seminary Foundation
MacLean, George E. --- Director, British Division of the American University Union
Makanya, Violet
Mann, Charles R. --- American Council on Education
Manning, The Rt. Rev. William Thomas --- Bishop of New York
Martine, E. --- Secretary of the Finance Committee, Tuskegee Institute
Marvin, Cloyd H. --- President of George Washington University
Mason, Max --- Rockefeller Foundation
Maxwell, George L. --- National Council on Religion in Higher Education
McClenahan, Robert S. --- President of American University, Cairo, Egypt
McCormick, Robert R. --- The Chicago Tribune
McCormick, Vance
McCulloch, James W. --- Phelps-Stokes Estates, finances
McFarland, Ross A. --- National Council on Religion in Higher Education
Meeks, Everett Victor --- Professor of Architecture, School of Fine Arts, Yale University
Mellon, Andrew W. --- U.S. Secretary of the Treasury
Mendell, Clarence W. --- Dean of Yale College
Meriam, Lewis --- Survey of Indian Affairs
Mitchell, Anna V.S. --- Russian Refugee Relief Society
Mitchell, Clarence B.
Mitchell, Clarence V.S.
Moton, Robert R. --- Principal of Tuskegee Institute
Mott, John R. --- Y.M.C.A.: International Missionary Council
Murray, Wilfrid G.R. --- Registrar, University of Cape Town
Myers, George Hewitt --- re: Berea
Nansen, Fridtjof --- High Commissioner of Refugees of the League of Nations
National Council on Religion in Higher Education
Naylor, Irene M.A. --- Educational Commission to East Africa, Phelps-Stokes Fund
Nettleton, George H. --- American University Union; Yale University
Newbold, N.C. --- State Superintendent of Public Instruction, Raleigh, N.C.
Nicholson, A.W. --- Bettis Academy, South Carolina
Nicholson, Ralph --- National Cathedral Foundation
Noland, Charlotte H. --- Foxcroft School, Virginia
Noyes, Newbold --- The Evening Star, Washington, D.C.
Oldham, J.H. --- International Missionary Council
Olds, Marshall --- Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund; Peabody Educational Program
Olive, V.S. --- Russian refugee relief
Osborn, Minott --- United Hospital Fund of New York; Fiscal Service Corporation
Outhwaite, Leonard --- Laura-Spelman Rockefeller Memorial
Palmer, Archie --- Institute of International Education
Paton, William --- International Missionary Council
Patton, The Rev. Robert W. --- American Church Institute for Negroes
Payne, Bruce R. --- George Peabody College for Teachers
Payne, John Barton --- American Red Cross
Peabody, George Foster
Pearce, Dr. Richard M. --- China Medical Board of the Rockefeller Foundation
Perry, The Rt. Rev. James DeWolf --- Bishop of Rhode Island
Pepper, George Wharton --- Washington Cathedral Foundation
Peter, The Rev. G. Freeland --- Washington Cathedral
Phenix, George C. --- Hampton Institute
Pickens, William --- N.A.A.C.P.
Poland, William --- American Relief Administration
Pritchett, Henry S. --- President of the Carnegie Foundation for the Advancement of Teaching
Purrington, William A. --- re: repeal of Prohibition
Purves, Robert Ogden --- Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
Rammelkamp, Dr. C.H. --- President of Illinois College
Rand, E.K. --- Mediaeval Academy of America
Redfield, Humphrey D. --- National Cathedral Association
Rhinelander, The Rt. Rev. Philip --- National Cathedral Foundation; Washington Cathedral
Richards, Charles R. --- General Education Board
Ringland, Arthur C. --- American Relief Administration
Roberts, Louisa S. --- Washington Council of Social Agencies
Robertson, David A. --- American Council on Education
Rockefeller, John D. Jr.
Rogers, Henry Wade
Rogers, James Gamble
Roosevelt, Franklin Delano
Root, Elihu
Root, Mrs. Oren --- William Holland Wilmer Foundation
Rose, Dr. Wickliffe --- General Education Board
Rose, William J. --- Y.M.C.A. of Poland
Rosenwald, Julius --- Sears, Roebuck and Company
Rowe, L.S. --- Pan-American Union
Roy, L.A. --- Phelps-Stokes Fund
Ruggles, Alma L.H. --- Russian refugee relief
Ruml, Dr. Beardsley --- Laura-Spelman Rockefeller Foundation
Russell, James S. --- St. Paul Normal and Industrial School
Russell, William F. --- International Institute of Education
Sage, E.C. --- General Education Board
St. Anna's Church Home
Sakai, Barnabas T.
Sanders, Everett --- Secretary to the President of the U.S.
Schieffelin, William Jay --- Schieffelin and Company; Trustee of Hampton and Tuskegee Institutes
Schley, Reeve --- Vice President of the Chase National Bank; St. Paul's School
Scott, Emmett J. --- Secretary-Treasurer of Howard University
Scoville, William H. --- Secretary of Hampton Institute
Sedgwick, Ellery --- Editor of the Atlantic Monthly
Seymour, George Dudley
Shattuck, Dr. Frederick C. --- St. Paul's School
Shaw, Gardiner Howland --- Division of Near Eastern Affairs, U.S. Department of State
Sheldon, James
Sibley, James L. --- Phelps-Stokes Fund, Liberia
Simpson, R.H. --- American University Union in Europe
Slade, Francis Louis --- Phelps-Stokes Fund
Smith, Harvey Baker --- Washington Federation of Churches
Smith, William P. --- Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
Staub, Albert W. --- Fund for Near Eastern Colleges
Stern, Alfred K. --- Director of the Julius Rosenwald Fund
Stewart, The Rev. George Craig
Stewart, The Rev. George Jr.
Stimson, Henry L. --- U.S. Secretary of State
Stone, Harlan F. --- U.S. Supreme Court
Stowe, Beecher --- Doubleday, Doran and Company re: biography of James H. Dillard
Swift, Ernest J. --- The American Red Cross
Sze, Sao-Ke Alfred --- Chinese Ambassador to the U.S.
Taft, William Howard
Taylor, R.R. --- Tuskegee Institute
Taylor, William B. --- The American Red Cross
Terrell, Mary Church
Thompson, Henry B. --- American University Union
Thompson, Norma S. --- The Rockefeller Foundation
Thorn, Charlotte R. --- Calhoun Colored School, Calhoun, Ala.
Thorne, S. Brinckerhoff
Thorne, Samuel
Thwing, Charles F. --- President of Western Reserve University
Thurston, Matilda C. --- Ginling College, Nanking, China
Tigert, John J. --- U.S. Commissioner of Education
Tobias, C.H. --- National Council of the Y.M.C.A.
Tompkins, Ethel H. --- Secretary's Office, Yale University
Treadwell, Abbot --- St. Paul's School
Trudeau, Dr. Francis B. --- Trudeau Sanatorium
Turner, Fennel P. --- Foreign Missions Conference
Ufford, Walter S. --- The Associated Charities of Washington, D.C.
Van Santvoord, George --- The Hotchkiss School
Vickrey, Charles V. --- Near East Relief
Vincent, George E. --- The Rockefeller Foundation
Vreeland, Herbert H. --- Yale-in-China
Waggaman, Major Ennalls --- St. Anna's Church Home
Waite, Mary L. --- Institute of International Education
Wallace, The Rev. E.W. --- Committee for Christian Colleges in China
Warburg, Paul M. --- Hampton-Tuskegee Endowment Fund
Wardwell, Allen --- Russian refugee relief
Warnshuis, A.L. --- International Missionary Council
Warren, M. Frances --- Washington Council of Social Agencies
Washburn, Dr. Henry B. --- Dean of the Episcopal Theological School
Washington, Mrs. Booker T. --- Tuskegee Institute
Wheeler, W. Reginald --- The Board of Foreign Missions of the Presbyterian Church
White, Francis --- Assistant Secretary of State
White, Henry
White, Walter --- N.A.A.C.P.
Whittemore, Thomas --- Committee for the Education of Russian Youth in Exile
Williams, F. Wells --- Yale-in-China
Wiren, Alexis R. --- Russian Student Fund, Inc.
Wood, John Wilson --- National Council of the Protestant Episcopal Church
Wood, L. Hollingsworth
Woods, Arthur --- Laura-Spelman Rockefeller Foundation
Woodson, Carter G. --- The Journal of Negro History
Work, Monroe N. --- Tuskegee Institute; Editor of the Negro Year Book
Wyckoff, J. Edwards --- Butler, Wyckoff and Reid
Yen, Dr. F. C. --- Dean of the Medical School, Yale-in-China
Yen, Y.C. James --- Chinese National Association of the Mass Education Movement
Zwerner, L. --- Assistant High Commissioner for Refugees, League of Nations
SELECT LIST OF CORRESPONDENTS, 1930 Jun 1 - 1939 Dec 31
Acheson, Dean
The Afro-American
Aldrich, Malcolm P. --- Harkness Foundation
Alexander, Dr. Will W. --- Commission on Inter-Racial Co-operation
Allen, George E. --- Commissioner of the District of Columbia
American Peace Society
American Red Cross
Andrews, C.F. --- India
Anet, Henri --- Bureau des Missions Protestantes du Congo Belge
Angell, James Rowland --- President of Yale University
Archdall, The Rev. H.K. --- Kings College, Auckland, New Zealand
Arnett, Trevor --- General Education Board
Arnold, Lauren --- Yale-in-China
Asakawa, K. --- Yale University
Associated Charities of Washington, D.C.
Ballantine, Arthur A. --- Undersecretary of the Treasury
Ballou, Frank --- Superintendent of Schools, Washington, D.C.
Barclay, Edwin J. --- President of Liberia
Baskervill, The Rev. E.L.
Bartlett, The Very Rev. George G. --- Dean of Philadelphia Divinity School
Bates, Sanford --- Director of the Bureau of Prisons, U.S. Department of Justice
Baynes-Jones, Dr. S. --- Trumbull College of Yale University
Beers, Clifford W. --- National Committee for Mental Hygiene